A Guide to the William Ingham Papers, 1945-2013: SC 0002
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 7: Chronological Files, 1986-2013
  This series makes up the bulk of the collection and represents a monthly filing system kept by the donor. The series begins with a file comprised of two documents explaining Dr. Ingham's reasons for collecting and donating material related to the unrest at JMU during the 1990s. These two documents provide insight into the materials found in all subsequent series. Materials from the earliest years of 1986 - 1990 are grouped into one file, with the years 1991 and 1992 each representing one file. Beginning with January 1993 through December 1998, a file is kept for each month of each year. Within that span of years a few months are missing, most likely because the creator did not have materials for those months. January 1995 and February 1995 are the largest files and contain significant amounts of material related to the January 13, 1995 announcement by the JMU administration that the Physics major would be discontinued and the Physics Department disbanded. Other months that contain large amounts of material are April 1996 – relating to the honor code incident, and April 1997 - relating to the quashed subpoenas of Dr. Carrier and Zane Showker for the Jamie Raymond murder trial. See Box 96, Folder 1 for Ingham's explanation of the order of the files that includes details about the major events documented. This file is duplicated in Series 12: Subject Files, Box 110, Folder 21. Also of interest is the nine-page document entitled "NARRATIVE OF WILLIAM H. INGHAM'S ACTIVITIES AS A JMU FACULTY MEMBER WITH PARTICULAR REFERENCE TO ACTIONS, STATEMENTS, AND DOCUMENTS WHICH MIGHT HAVE ANGERED PRESIDENT OF OTHER JMU ADMINISTRATORS" found in folder May 1995 (Folder 1 of 2). Files entitled 1999-2001 and Miscellaneous Articles have been created by the archivist out of loose materials within the boxes. As many of the folders are titled by their date range, each folder title includes two date ranges: 1) the folder title itself as provided by the creator and 2) the date range of materials within the file which may include undated items.
  - Collection Background Information, 1998, 2013 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - 1986-1990, 1986-1990 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - 1991, 1991, undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - 1992 (folder 1 of 2), 1992, undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - 1992 (folder 2 of 2), 1992, undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - January 1993, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - February 1993, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - March 1993, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - April 1993, 1993, undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - May 1993, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - July 1993, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - August 1993, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - September 1993, 1993, undated (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - October 1993, 1993, undated (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - November 1993, 1993, undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - December 1993, 1993, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - January 1994, 1994, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - February 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - March 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - April 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - May 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - June 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - July 1994, 1994, undated (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - August 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - September 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - October 1994, 1994, undated (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - November 1994, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - December 1994, 1994, undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - January 1995 (folder 1 of 3), 1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - January 1995 (folder 2 of 3), 1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - January 1995 (folder 3 of 3), 1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - February 1995 (folder 1 of 4), 1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - February 1995 (folder 2 of 4), 1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - February 1995 (folder 3 of 4), 1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - February 1995 (folder 4 of 4), 1995, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - March 1995 (folder 1 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - March 1995 (folder 2 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - April 1995 (folder 1 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - April 1995 (folder 2 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - May 1995 (folder 1 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - May 1995 (folder 2 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - June 1995, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - July 1995, 1995, undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - August 1995 (folder 1 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - August 1995 (folder 2 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - September 1995 (folder 1 of 3), 1995, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - September 1995 (folder 2 of 3), 1995, undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - September 1995 (folder 3 of 3), 1995, undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - October 1995, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - November 1995, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - December 1995, 1995, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - January 1996 (folder 1 of 2), 1995-1997, undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - January 1996 (folder 2 of 2), 1995-1997, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - February 1996, 1996, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - March 1996, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - April 1996 (folder 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - April 1996 (folder 2 of 2), 1996 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - May 1996 (folder 1 of 2), 1996, undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - May 1996 (folder 2 of 2), 1996, undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - June 1996, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - July 1996, 1996, undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - August 1996, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - September 1996, 1996, undated (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - October 1996, 1996, undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - November 1996, 1996, undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - December 1996, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - January 1997, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - February 1997, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - March 1997, 1997, undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - April 1997, 1997, undated (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - May 1997, 1997, undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - June 1997, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - July 1997, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - August 1997, 1997, undated (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - September 1997, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - October 1997, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - November 1997, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - December 1997, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - February 1998, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - March 1998, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - April 1998, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - May 1998, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - June 1998, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - July 1998, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - August 1998, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - November-December 1998, 1998-1999 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - 1999-2007, 1999-2007 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 2008-2013 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Series 8: Faculty for Responsible Change, 1993-2008
  Arranged in two sub-series. Series 8.1: Lawsuit Files is arranged alphabetically. Series 8.2: Exhibit Items is arranged numerically by exhibit number.
  This series comprises materials related to the aftermath of the January 13, 1995 announcement of academic restructuring, specifically that the Physics Department and major would be eliminated along with ten faculty positions. Materials specifically concern the activities of the group Faculty for Responsible Change (FRC), of which Dr. Ingham was a member, including its lawsuit against the James Madison University Board of Visitors. The first two folders in this series contain materials – newspaper clippings, memoranda, correspondence, timelines – that put into context the January 13 announcement including the lead-up (move to restructure the university, Carrier appoints son Michael as assistant provost of CISAT) and details the immediate aftermath. The donor labeled items submitted as exhibits in the lawsuit FRC v. JMU Visitors numerically D1-D149. These exhibit items include memoranda, correspondence, and newspaper clippings. Subseries 8.1 is comprised of general lawsuit files and Subseries 8.2 is individually numbered exhibit items which include correspondence, newspaper clippings, etc.
  - Subseries 8.1: Lawsuit Files, 1993-2008
    - 1-13-95 Articles and Documents (folder 1 of 2), January 1995-October 1995 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - 1-13-95 Articles and Documents (folder 2 of 2), January 1995-October 1995 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - DWP – Statements and Supporting Documents, 1993-1995 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - FRC Materials, 1993-1995, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - FRC Materials, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - FRC, 2008 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Hogshire, 1995, undated (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - JN Deposition, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Lawsuit Documents and Event Timelines, 1995, undated (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Master Chronology FRC v. JMU, 1995, undated (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Narrative of Ingham's Activities as a JMU Faculty Member, ca. 1995 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Official JMU Referendum Ballot (Dec. 8-9, 1993), ca. 1993 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Original Petition Signatures, ca. December 1993 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - People, Petition Drafts, Phone Numbers, etc., December 1993, undated (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Procedures for Referendum, Including Eligible Lists, December 1993, undated (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Referendum – Eligible for Interim Election Committee, December 1993, undated (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Requests of Records/Memos from FRC Lawyers, 1993-1995 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Tallies, December 1993, undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - W. H. I as Irritant, 1993-1995 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 8.2: Exhibit Items, 1993-1995
    - D1-D149 – Exhibit Item List, ca. 1995 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - D1-D20 (8/7/93-10/21/93), August 1993-December 1993 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - D21-D40 (10/28/93-12/6/93), October 1993-December 1993 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - D41-D67B (12/6/93-8/25/94), December 1993-August 1994 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - D68-D90 (9/1/94-1/18/95), September 1994-January 1995 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - D91-D110 (1/18/95-1/30/95), January 1995 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - D111-D127 (1/30/95-3/1/95), January 1995-March 1995 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - D130-D149 (3/3/95-5/3/95), March 1995-May 1995 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Series 9: General Education, 1993-1998
  The materials within the General Education series relate to the work of the General Education Committee, of which Ingham was a member from the committee's inception to its dissolution. The committee was established in February 1994, after the Liberal Studies Review Committee completed an external review of the Liberal Studies Program and suggested the establishment of a committee to complete an in-depth examination of the Liberal Studies Program and to make suggestions for modifications to the program as a part of the larger restructuring taking place at JMU. See folder GENED January 1994 for the initial report of the Liberal Studies Review Committee, and folder GENED May 1994 for a history of the General Education Committee. Materials in this series include meeting minutes and agendas from the General Education Committee, email and written communications among committee members as well as members of the administration, print-outs of posts to the electronic bulletin board, planning documents, course proposals, and reports.
  Originally, these materials were contained in several large folders labeled GENED and organized chronologically within the folders. For ease of use, the materials were kept in the original order, but organized into smaller folders by month and year. In addition to the GENED folders there are also several folders of material labeled topically. These were kept in original order and filed within the chronological arrangement.
  - GENED January 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - GENED Pilot Proposals (folder 1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - GENED Pilot Proposals (folder 2 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Approval Process for GENED, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - GENED February 1994, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - GENED March 1994, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - GENED April 1994, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - GENED May 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - GENED June 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - GENED July 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - GENED August 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - GENED September 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - GENED October 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - GENED November 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - GENED December 1994, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - GE, 1994-1995 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - GENED January 1995, 1995, undated (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - GENED Proposal from Dawn Fisher, January 1995, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - GENED February 1995, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - GENED March 1995, 1995, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - GENED April 1995, 1995, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - GENED May 1995, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - GENED July-August 1995, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - GENED 1996-1998, 1996-1998 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Physics Program Review, 1990-1999
  Materials from this series relate to the Physics Department Academic Program Review (APR) that occurred following the January 13, 1995 announcement of the dissolution of the Physics Department and subsequent reinstatement of the major. Materials include documents used to create the Academic Program Review Report (for the full report see folder titled James Madison University Physics Department Academic Program Review, July 1995), email, and other communications about the APR, faculty meeting minutes, and reports. A large portion of this series consists of the surveys sent to Physics Departments at institutions identified as "peer" institutions to JMU. This series also includes the 1997 Physics Department Strategic Plan which addresses the August 1995 External Team Report on recommendations for change to the undergraduate Physics program. This report is contained in folder titled Program Review Information Packet: James Madison University Department of Physics February 21-22, 1999.
  - Physics Faculty Member Data, 1990-1995 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Liberal Arts Physics, 1992-1995 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Academic Program Review 1993-94, May 1994 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Statistical Summaries – Office of Institutional Research, 1994-1995 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Physics Department Discussion Boards, February 1995 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – SUNY Brockport, April 17, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – University of Wisconsin Oshkosh, April 17, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Baylor University, April 18, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Middle Tennessee State University, April 18, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Appalachian State University, May 1, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – University of Tennessee at Chattanooga, May 2, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Western Michigan University, May 5, 1995 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – California State University, Fresno, May 15, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – California State University, Sacramento, June 2, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Illinois State University, June 2, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – SUNY Plattsburgh, June 12, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – University of North Carolina, Charlotte, June 27, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – California State University, Chico, June 28, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Indiana State University, June 29, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Western Illinois University, June 29, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – James Madison University, ca. June 1995 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – Sonoma State University, ca. June 1995 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – University of Southern Mississippi, ca. June 1995 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Survey of Physics Departments – University of Wisconsin – Eau Claire, ca. June 1995 (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - 1995 Physics Program Review/Revisions (folder 1 of 2), 1992-1995 (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - 1995 Physics Program Review/Revisions (folder 2 of 2), 1992-1995 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Full AIP Spreadsheet, July 5, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Assessing the Physics Major at JMU: 1993-95 Summary Report, July 1995 (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - James Madison University Physics Department Academic Program Review, July 1995 (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Survey of JMU Physics Graduates, July 1995, undated (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Statistics on Baccalaureate Physics Degrees, 1995, 1998, undated (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Program Review Information Packet: James Madison University Department of Physics February 21-22, 1999, February 1999 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- Series 11: Reports, 1989-1996
  This series is comprised exclusively of reports relating to the charge issued by the Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on the University of the 21st Century to create innovative approaches to education in preparation for the inevitable influx of students expected to enter Virginia's higher education system in the coming century. JMU's response to this charge included a restructuring of academic programs and the creation of the College of Integrated Science and Technology (CISAT). These reports include Dr. Ingham's handwritten annotations. Portions are also marked as significant in some way with Post-It Notes. Of particular interest is the May 1989 Case Study of the Organizational Dynamics for Teaching and Learning prepared for the National Center for Research to Improve Postsecondary Teaching Learning (NCRIPTAL) at the University of Michigan. Dr. Ingham made extensive annotations to this report which comments on, among other things, the academic culture of JMU and particularly the role of Dr. Carrier and a few senior administrators.
  - Case Study of the Organizational Dynamics for Teaching and Learning at James Madison University, May 1989 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Issue Two – To What End: Learning How to Learn – Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on the University of the 21st Century, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Issue Three – Business and Education - Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on the University of the 21st Century, ca. 1989 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Issue Four – Knowledge and Self – Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on the University of the 21st Century, ca. 1989 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Issue Five – Blueprints for Organization – Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on the University of the 21st Century, ca. 1989 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Issue Six – The Case for Change – Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on the University of the 21st Century, ca. 1989 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - The Case for Change – Draft – Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on the University of the 21st Century, ca. 1989 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Proposal for James Madison University College of Applied Science and Technology – Executive Summary, December 1990 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for James Madison University College of Applied Science and Technology – Executive Summary and Technical Report, December 1990 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Response to the Report of the Commission on the University of the 21st Century, May 1991 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - U21 Issues Affecting the Future of Virginia's Colleges and Universities, 1993-1994 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Statistical Summary, James Madison University Office of Institutional Research, 1993-1994, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Restructuring Plan – James Madison University, ca. 1994 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Guidelines for Higher Education Fixed Assets for Educational and General Programs, Nov. 3, 1994, 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Report of the Substantive Change Committee – JMU Harrisonburg, VA, January 29-February 1, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Statistical Summary Office of Institutional Research, 1994-1995, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Chichester Report, January 1996 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- Series 12: Subject Files, 1992-2013
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  The Subject Files series represents the files within the collection that did not have any arrangement when received from the donor. See Box 110, Folder 21 for Ingham's explanation of the order of the files that includes details about the major events documented. This file is duplicated in Series 7: Chronological Files, Box 96, Folder 1. Most of the material within the Subject Files series relates to issues and events represented in the Chronological Files series. However, some files are of a general nature and relate to the day-to-day operations of the JMU Physics Department. These files are labeled topically and represent a variety of topics. Folders labeled CS-APPT refer to the Chesapeake Section of the American Association of Physics Teachers, of which Dr. Ingham was a member.
  Materials cover topics including JMU's transition from liberal studies to a general education curriculum, the academic restructuring of the mid-1990s, faculty handbook revisions, satirical artwork prominently featuring Dr. Carrier, materials relating to Dr. Ingham's November 1998 presentation at the Chesapeake Section for the American Association of Physics Teachers (CSAAPT) entitled Trends in Baccalaureate Degree Production in Physics, and the Jamie Raymond murder trial. Materials related to the Raymond case include copies of court transcripts, written exhibits, other court documents, and an exhaustive and thorough collection of newspaper clippings.
  Included in this series are a small number of folders labeled as Physics Department – G Chron. According to the creator, the "G Chron" refers to General Files – Chronological, and the label was added at a later date in a planned reorganization of the files by the creator that did not come to be. Because of the small number of these "G Chron" labeled folders, the archivist elected to arrange them alphabetically within the subject files series.
  - 11/30/95 – AAUP Conference on Restructuring, 1995, undated (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Anonymous Correspondence, 1999 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Artwerk, 1995, undated (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Collection Background Information, 1998, 2013 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - CS-AAPT 11/21/98 refs., 1995-1996, 1998-1999, undated (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - CS-AAPT Spring 1996, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - CS-AAPT 11/21/98 Transparencies, 1998, undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Education Reform – Revised Draft, 1999 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - 1994 Faculty Forum New Approaches to Teaching and Learning, 1994, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Handbook Revisions, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - 1995-1996 Faculty Recruitment Handbook, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate, 1998, 2000 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Gender Equity Committee, 1994-1995, undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - ISAT Energy Sector Group, 1995 (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Jamie Raymond – Allen letter, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Jamie Raymond Case, 1997 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Jamie Raymond Case – Articles, 1997, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Jamie Raymond Case Court Documents (folder 1 of 2), 1997, undated (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Jamie Raymond Case Court Documents (folder 2 of 2), 1997, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - JMU's Transition from Liberal Studies to General Education: Core Issues and Outcomes, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - John Kl., 1995, 1997 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Kohen essay, ca. 2001 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - LHR, 1996, 2000, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Liberal Studies 101 – email and communications, 1993, undated (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Linwood Rose articles, 1998 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - 1990 Madison Conference, ca. 2013 (Box 112, Folder 8)